<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mark Mukhin</title>
    <link>https://23chase.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mark Mukhin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2022, Mark Mukhin.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 18:23:23 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://23chase.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to gain muscle mass on a vegan diet?</title>
      <link>https://23chase.github.io/texts/vegan-diet101/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2022 18:23:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://23chase.github.io/texts/vegan-diet101/</guid>
      <description>For more than 2 years I train regularly, trying not to skip working out. I see progress, but it does not match invested efforts. One of the factors that may impact my workout performance significantly is my diet. And I am not sure, that my nutrition is balanced with my goals.
What goals do I have? My goal is to maintain a high overall level of health, to live longer, maintain advanced energy and focus, strength, mobility and flexibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>App Marketing predictions using MMM.</title>
      <link>https://23chase.github.io/texts/app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 18:23:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://23chase.github.io/texts/app/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: I am not a statistician. I always worked with app marketing. I wrote wrote this text for people like me — for who don’t know much about linear regression and stuff. Some of these techniques I tried, most of them not. But I wanna to explore it to answer some questions that important for me.
What is MMM? Marketing Mix Modeling is an analysis of historical marketing data to estimate the impact of marketing channels and activities on sales and forecast the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Muscular flexibility is underrated. Why?</title>
      <link>https://23chase.github.io/texts/flexibility101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 18:23:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://23chase.github.io/texts/flexibility101/</guid>
      <description>I am not flexible. I can&amp;rsquo;t even touch my toes. A few years ago I had back pain. Manual therapist said that I have weak back muscles, and this will impact my future life. He even advised me not to lift weights heavier than 5 kg. Now I am recovered, but sometimes it reminds me of itself.
I wondered — now I am in my late 20s. I can’t touch my toes, sometimes I have unbearable pain when I can’t roll out of bed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
