<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mark Mukhin</title>
    <link>https://23chase.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mark Mukhin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2022, Mark Mukhin.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 14:23:23 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://23chase.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Diving into AI-Powered Music Production</title>
      <link>https://23chase.github.io/texts/ai-music-production-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 14:23:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://23chase.github.io/texts/ai-music-production-1/</guid>
      <description>When ChatGPT was released in November 2022, it got hundreds of potential implications—you can get answer to almost any question, get ready-made essay on specified subject, working programming code or compiling business strategy. And the quality of the output depends mostly only on how good you are at asking in the right way. One of the first thoughts I had was: how can we use the coming wave of generative AI in music production?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All Apps Are Special</title>
      <link>https://23chase.github.io/texts/all-apps-are-special/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 18:23:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://23chase.github.io/texts/all-apps-are-special/</guid>
      <description>My first smartphone was an iPhone 3GS. I remember when apps were something cool and novel. You asked friends, read reviews and tried to find standout experiences. In 2017, I had a choice of becoming a more traditional web advertising manager or going all in on app ads. I was smart enough to choose the latter. And I&amp;rsquo;m happy to have the opportunity to promote many incredible products. For me, it&amp;rsquo;s important to work with companies that empower people, open up new opportunities or solve everyday problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to combat deepfakes technology?</title>
      <link>https://23chase.github.io/texts/combat-deepfakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 18:23:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://23chase.github.io/texts/combat-deepfakes/</guid>
      <description>Artificial Intelligence (AI) improvement is fraught with danger at a high-level —economical, ethical, existential. We have heard alarming notes from researchers such as Bostrom and Hawking, and from businessmen such as Gates and Musk. However, the rapid rise of low-level, day-to-day implementations also brings concerns. Tools to create fake realities are becoming increasingly accessible, and these can be very harmful.
Someone can already create fake images or videos of a person, or even attend online calls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overcoming the Challenges of Answer Search Engines</title>
      <link>https://23chase.github.io/texts/answer-search-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 18:23:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://23chase.github.io/texts/answer-search-engine/</guid>
      <description>The Generative Pre-trained Transformers (GPT) family of large language models has been rapidly improving. These language models are trained on data that humankind has produced, giving us access to the collective wisdom of the ages, but faster and more accurately. GPT-3, released in mid-2020, was a breakthrough and has enabled a range of text-based projects of varying complexity. The release of ChatGPT in late 2022 has further pushed the boundaries, although AI still has some limitations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ageing Population Opportunities</title>
      <link>https://23chase.github.io/texts/ageing-population-opportunities/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 18:23:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://23chase.github.io/texts/ageing-population-opportunities/</guid>
      <description>The human populace has multiplied exponentially — from 1 billion to 8 billion within two centuries. From 1960, the rise became swift — population has augmented by one billion every 10-15 years, largely due to dropping infant mortality rates. By the mid-21st century, it is expected to reach 10 billion. Because of that, in the 20th century, governments have been alarmed, believing that growth needs to be reduced to ensure enough food and living space for everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Make Smart Assistant Smarter And Stay Private?</title>
      <link>https://23chase.github.io/texts/smart-assistants/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 18:23:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://23chase.github.io/texts/smart-assistants/</guid>
      <description>I was inspired by this thread of comments and came to some conclusions around future of virtual assistants — https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33608437
I am passionate about the idea of intelligent virtual assistant, like many people around here. This widespread obsession is visible through countless examples from popular culture — HAL 9000 and Jarvis, Skynet and Batcomputer. What’s so attractive about it? Virtual assistant represent the companion, who’s power complement human’s, and help one to become a superhuman, with limitless capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>App Marketing predictions using MMM</title>
      <link>https://23chase.github.io/texts/app-marketing-predictions-using-mmm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 18:23:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://23chase.github.io/texts/app-marketing-predictions-using-mmm/</guid>
      <description>What is MMM? Marketing Mix Modeling is an analysis of historical marketing data to estimate the impact of marketing channels and activities on sales and forecast the future.
Put it simple: We wanna know, how our budget works.
Why anybody should care about it? In terms of marketing, it is not always possible to say, that Channel X caused Y increase in sales in Z time. Everything starts with non-trackable ads, or ads that very difficult to track, like TV or billboards.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
