<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>privacy on Mark Mukhin</title>
    <link>https://23chase.github.io/texts/privacy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in privacy on Mark Mukhin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2022, Mark Mukhin.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 18:23:23 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://23chase.github.io/texts/privacy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to combat deepfakes technology?</title>
      <link>https://23chase.github.io/texts/combat-deepfakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 18:23:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://23chase.github.io/texts/combat-deepfakes/</guid>
      <description>Artificial Intelligence (AI) improvement is fraught with danger at a high-level —economical, ethical, existential. We have heard alarming notes from researchers such as Bostrom and Hawking, and from businessmen such as Gates and Musk. However, the rapid rise of low-level, day-to-day implementations also brings concerns. Tools to create fake realities are becoming increasingly accessible, and these can be very harmful.
Someone can already create fake images or videos of a person, or even attend online calls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Make Smart Assistant Smarter And Stay Private?</title>
      <link>https://23chase.github.io/texts/smart-assistants/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 18:23:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://23chase.github.io/texts/smart-assistants/</guid>
      <description>I was inspired by this thread of comments and came to some conclusions around future of virtual assistants — https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33608437
I am passionate about the idea of intelligent virtual assistant, like many people around here. This widespread obsession is visible through countless examples from popular culture — HAL 9000 and Jarvis, Skynet and Batcomputer. What’s so attractive about it? Virtual assistant represent the companion, who’s power complement human’s, and help one to become a superhuman, with limitless capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
