<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>future on Mark Mukhin</title>
    <link>https://23chase.github.io/texts/future/</link>
    <description>Recent content in future on Mark Mukhin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2022, Mark Mukhin.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 18:23:23 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://23chase.github.io/texts/future/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Overcoming the Challenges of Answer Search Engines</title>
      <link>https://23chase.github.io/texts/answer-search-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 18:23:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://23chase.github.io/texts/answer-search-engine/</guid>
      <description>The Generative Pre-trained Transformers (GPT) family of large language models has been rapidly improving. These language models are trained on data that humankind has produced, giving us access to the collective wisdom of the ages, but faster and more accurately. GPT-3, released in mid-2020, was a breakthrough and has enabled a range of text-based projects of varying complexity. The release of ChatGPT in late 2022 has further pushed the boundaries, although AI still has some limitations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ageing Population Opportunities</title>
      <link>https://23chase.github.io/texts/ageing-population-opportunities/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 18:23:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://23chase.github.io/texts/ageing-population-opportunities/</guid>
      <description>The human populace has multiplied exponentially — from 1 billion to 8 billion within two centuries. From 1960, the rise became swift — population has augmented by one billion every 10-15 years, largely due to dropping infant mortality rates. By the mid-21st century, it is expected to reach 10 billion. Because of that, in the 20th century, governments have been alarmed, believing that growth needs to be reduced to ensure enough food and living space for everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Make Smart Assistant Smarter And Stay Private?</title>
      <link>https://23chase.github.io/texts/smart-assistants/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 18:23:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://23chase.github.io/texts/smart-assistants/</guid>
      <description>I was inspired by this thread of comments and came to some conclusions around future of virtual assistants — https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=33608437
I am passionate about the idea of intelligent virtual assistant, like many people around here. This widespread obsession is visible through countless examples from popular culture — HAL 9000 and Jarvis, Skynet and Batcomputer. What’s so attractive about it? Virtual assistant represent the companion, who’s power complement human’s, and help one to become a superhuman, with limitless capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Data Do We Lose Now?</title>
      <link>https://23chase.github.io/texts/what-data-do-we-lose-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 18:23:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://23chase.github.io/texts/what-data-do-we-lose-now/</guid>
      <description>What data do we gather? We gather a vast amount of data — the total amount gathered up to 2020 is 64,2 zettabytes, and till 2025 it will reach 180 zettabytes. There are some of the fields:
Users behavior online. We get from search, socials, communication platforms, e-com stores, payment providers. It gives information about what our society is looking for, what we are capturing, and how we behave in the real-time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
